

# WALEED AHMAD Web Developer

House No 15 Al-Hafiz Town Near

Marghazar Colony Multan Road
- Lahore

☑ wal33dm5@gmail.com

**&** +92 309 943300

# SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/wal33d-ahmad

Waleed-M5

## PROFILE

I am a person, responsible with their work during working hours. I am a good timekeeper, always willing to learn new skills. I have several months of experience as salesman. I am also learning full stack web development course in which my experience is 7 months.

## EDUCATION

MATRIC

American Lyceum School 2016 - 2018

🕨 F.A

Degree College 2018 - 2020

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Pny Training - Arfa Tower 2022 - Current

#### SKILLS

- Html
- Mongo db
- Css
- Express

## EXPERIENCE

#### SALEMAN IN PHARMACY

From 2018 - 2019 | Pharmiz Pharmacy

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

# Full Stack WEB Developer

From 2022 - Current | Arfa Tower

I started my course at the beginning of this year and have gained a lot of experience so far. While learning web development course I have completed some projects some of which I am going to share with you.

## **PROJECTS**

#### **TextUtils**

TextUtils is a word counter and a character counting utility which can be used to manipulate your text in the way you want. You can remove extra spaces, copy the manipulated text as well as covert your text from uppercase to lowercase, & lowercase to uppercase.

# Google Keep Clone

Keep Clone is project, made for practicing my skills and show up a fully functionaing JavaScript clone for google keep This is a Google Keep inspired, Notes keeping app. The best part? All the notes you save are kept locally on your computer!

## NewsApp

NewsApp can be used to grab quick daily news bites from worldwide in this app you can easily read news articles and explore the world.

## REFERENCES

No Reference

#### LANGUAGES

EnglishUrdu

## INTERESTS

Gaming Programming Travel Learning

- JavaScript React
- Mern Stack